{
    "en-us": {
        "saveAt": "Saved at",
        "location": "Location: ",
        "newSession": "New Session",
        "restore": "Restore",
        "delete": "Delete",
        "restoreAndDel": "Restore & Delete",
        "contact": "Contact",
        "settings": "Settings",
        "back": "Back",
        "about": "About",
        "all": "All",
        "movePrompt": "Move session",
        "tagPrompt": "Add tags here...",
        "editPrompt": "Edit session",
        "topPrompt": "Move to top",
        "mergePrompt": "Merge with session...",
        "whatsNew": "What's <strong style='color: salmon'>New</strong>",
        "export": "Export",
        "import": "Import",
        "cancel": "Cancel",
        "exportTitle": "Tab Space Exported Tabs",
        "exportHTML": "Export as HTML",
        "exportJSON": "Export backup file",
        "exportText": "Copy as Text",
        "exportMD": "Copy as Markdown",
        "loseTabs": "Lost your tabs? Maybe Tab Space just upgraded, please wait for a moment and refresh ...",
        "manuallyMigrate": "Manually migrate sessions before Tab Space 3.5",
        "migrateTip": "Or go to settings and manually migrate old sessions",
        "tips": "Tips:",
        "tipContents": [
            "If you hit \"save tabs\" and found no tabs were saved, it is because Tab Space just upgraded, please restart Safari to enable it. ",
            "Your sessions are now synced across all your devices with iCloud. (macOS 10.15 required)",
            "You can now use Drag and Drop to reorganize your sessions or sites.",
            "Please rate Tab Space on Mac App Store if you like this app.",
            "Tab Space shortcuts will not work when Safari address bar is empty. Because empty address bar means a special page where extension could not be loaded."
        ],
        "loading": "loading...",
        "ignore-pinned-tabs": "Ignore pinned web pages while saving tabs",
        "ignore-duplicated-tabs": "Don't save duplicated tabs (even for those in different sessions)",
        "save-all-windows": "Save tabs from all windows",
        "shift-shortcuts": "Trigger shortcuts with Ctrl + Shift",
        "disable-shortcuts": "Disable shortcuts",
        "disable-context-menus": "Disable context menus",
        "remove-site-after-click": "Remove saved tab from the session when you click it",
        "shortcuts": "Shortcuts",
        "shortcutTip": "Note: shortcuts do not work when Safari address bar is empty.",
        "ctrlL": "Close left tabs",
        "ctrlR": "Close right tabs",
        "ctrlQ": "Close all other tabs",
        "ctrlC": "Open in Chrome",
        "ctrlW": "Open in Edge",
        "ctrlF": "Open in Firefox",
        "ctrlI": "Open in Brave Browser",
        "ctrlT": "Open Tab Space",
        "ctrlB": "Save selected text to Bear",
        "goTip": "If you just want to set Tab Space as the default page of new tab, please use the address \"http://mytab.space/redirect.html\".",
        "saveAndCloseTabs": "Save & Close Tabs",
        "saveAndKeepTabs": "Save & Keep Tabs",
        "saveCurrentTab": "Save Current Tab",
        "recentlySaved": "Recently Saved",
        "favorites": "Favorites",
        "activeTabs": "Active Tabs",
        "openSafariPref": "Open in Safari Extension Preferences",
        "appIntroduction": "Born for improving your web browsing productivity.",
        "upgradeSafari": "Tab Space requires at least Safari 12.1.\n Please upgrade your Safari."
    },
    "zh-cn": {
        "saveAt": "保存于",
        "location": "位置：",
        "newSession": "新会话",
        "restore": "恢复",
        "delete": "删除",
        "restoreAndDel": "恢复并删除",
        "contact": "联系我们",
        "settings": "设置",
        "back": "返回",
        "about": "关于",
        "all": "全部",
        "movePrompt": "移动会话",
        "tagPrompt": "添加标签...",
        "editPrompt": "编辑会话",
        "topPrompt": "移动到顶部",
        "mergePrompt": "合并会话...",
        "whatsNew": "<strong style='color: salmon'>新功能</strong>",
        "export": "导出",
        "import": "导入",
        "cancel": "取消",
        "exportTitle": "Tab Space 导出标签页",
        "exportHTML": "导出为 HTML",
        "exportJSON": "导出备份文件",
        "exportText": "复制为文字",
        "exportMD": "复制为 Markdown",
        "loseTabs": "标签页不见了？可能是 Tab Space 刚刚更新，请稍侯刷新...",
        "manuallyMigrate": "手动迁移 Tab Space 3.5 之前保存的会话",
        "migrateTip": "或进入设置页面手动迁移旧数据",
        "tips": "提示：",
        "tipContents": [
            "如果您发现点击“保存”按钮后标签页没有被保存，这很可能是由于 Tab Space 刚刚更新，重启 Safari 以使其生效即可恢复正常。",
            "您的书签组现通过 iCloud 在设备间同步。(要求 macOS 10.15 版本）",
            "您现在可以通过拖拽保存的会话或站点以重新组织您的记录。",
            "如果您喜欢 Tab Space，请在 Mac App Store 进行评分。",
            "Tab Space 在 Safari 地址栏为空时无法使用，因为空地址栏意味着当前处于插件无法访问的特殊页面。"
        ],
        "loading": "加载中...",
        "ignore-pinned-tabs": "保存标签时忽略置顶页",
        "ignore-duplicated-tabs": "不保存重复的标签页（即使是在不同的会话中重复）",
        "save-all-windows": "点击时保存所有窗口的标签页",
        "shift-shortcuts": "使用 Ctrl + Shift 触发快捷键",
        "disable-shortcuts": "禁用快捷键",
        "disable-context-menus": "禁用右键菜单",
        "remove-site-after-click": "点击保存的标签页时将它从会话中移除",
        "shortcuts": "快捷键",
        "shortcutTip": "注意：Safari 地址栏为空时快捷键无法使用。",
        "ctrlL": "关闭左侧标签页",
        "ctrlR": "关闭右侧标签页",
        "ctrlQ": "关闭其它所有标签页",
        "ctrlC": "用 Chrome 打开当前标签页",
        "ctrlW": "用 Edge 打开当前标签页",
        "ctrlF": "用 Firefox 打开当前标签页",
        "ctrlI": "用 Brave 浏览器打开当前标签页",
        "ctrlT": "打开 Tab Space",
        "ctrlB": "保存选中文字到 Bear 熊掌记",
        "goTip": "如果您想设置 Tab Space 为默认的新标签页，请使用地址“http://mytab.space/redirect.html”。",
        "saveAndCloseTabs": "保存并关闭所有标签页",
        "saveAndKeepTabs": "保存所有标签页",
        "saveCurrentTab": "保存当前标签页",
        "recentlySaved": "最近保存",
        "favorites": "收藏",
        "activeTabs": "活动标签页",
        "openSafariPref": "打开 Safari 扩展设置",
        "appIntroduction": "为提高网络浏览效率而生的 Safari 扩展",
        "upgradeSafari": "Tab Space 要求 Safari 12.1 或更高版本\n 请升级您的 Safari 浏览器"
    },
    "uk": {
        "saveAt": "Збережено",
        "restore": "Відновити",
        "delete": "Видалити",
        "restoreAndDel": "Відновити і видалити",
        "contact": "Контакти",
        "settings": "Налаштування",
        "back": "Назад",
        "about": "Про автора",
        "all": "Всі",
        "tagPrompt": "Додати теги...",
        "export": "Експорт",
        "import": "Імпорт",
        "cancel": "Скасувати",
        "exportTitle": "Вкладки експортовані Tab Space",
        "exportHTML": "Експортувати як HTML",
        "exportJSON": "Експортувати файл бекапу",
        "exportText": "Копіювати як текст",
        "exportMD": "Копіювати як Markdown",
        "loseTabs": "Загубили свої вкладки? Можливо, Tab Space тільки-но обновлено, будь ласка, трохи зачекайте...",
        "manuallyMigrate": "Ручна міграція сеансів перед Tab Space 3.5",
        "migrateTip": "Або перейдіть до налаштувань і вручну перемістіть старі сеанси",
        "tips": "Поради:",
        "loading": "завантаження...",
        "ignore-pinned-tabs": "Ігнорувати прикріплені вкладки при збереженні",
        "save-all-windows": "Зберігати вкладки з усіх вікон",
        "disable-shortcuts": "Вимкнути швидкі комбінації",
        "shortcuts": "Швидкі комбінації",
        "shortcutTip": "Примітка: швидкі комбінації вимкнені, якщо адресний рядок у Safari є порожнім.",
        "ctrlL": "Закрити вкладки зліва",
        "ctrlR": "Закрити вкладки справа",
        "ctrlQ": "Закрити всі інші вкладки",
        "ctrlC": "Відкрити в Chrome",
        "ctrlF": "Відкрити в Firefox",
        "ctrlI": "Відкрити в Brave",
        "ctrlT": "Відкрити Tab Space",
        "ctrlB": "Зберегти виділений текст до Bear",
        "goTip": "Якщо Ви хочете запускати Tab Space по замовчуванню на новій вкладці, будь ласка використайте для неї адресу \"http://mytab.space/redirect.html\".",
        "saveAndCloseTabs": "Зберегти і закрити вкладки",
        "saveAndKeepTabs": "Зберегти і залишити вкладки",
        "saveCurrentTab": "Зберегти поточну вкладку",
        "openSafariPref": "Відкрити в налаштуваннях розширень Safari",
        "appIntroduction": "Народжений для покращення Вашої продуктивності у веб-браузингу."
    },
    "es": {
        "saveAt": "Guardar como",
        "restore": "Restaurar",
        "delete": "Borrar",
        "restoreAndDel": "Restaurar y Borrar",
        "contact": "Contactar",
        "settings": "Preferencias",
        "back": "Atrás",
        "about": "Acerca de",
        "all": "Todo",
        "tagPrompt": "Agregar etiquetas aquí...",
        "export": "Exportar",
        "import": "Importar",
        "cancel": "Cancelar",
        "exportTitle": "Pestañas Tab Space Exportadas",
        "exportHTML": "Exportar como HTML",
        "exportJSON": "Exportar archivo de respaldo",
        "exportText": "Copiar como texto",
        "exportMD": "Copiar como Markdown",
        "loseTabs": "¿Perdiste tus pestañas? Quizás Tab Space acaba de actualizarse, por favor espera un momento y dale refrescar a Safari...",
        "manuallyMigrate": "Migrar sesiones manualmente a Tab Space 3.5",
        "migrateTip": "O vaya a la configuración y migre manualmente las sesiones antiguas",
        "tips": "Tips:",
        "tipContents": [
            "Si pulsaste \"guardar pestañas\" y las pestañas no se guardaron puede ser porque Tab Space ha sido actualizado recientemente. Por favor reinica Safari para habilitarlo. ",
            "Tus sesiones están ahora sincronizadas con todos tus dispositivos utilizando iCloud. (macOS 10.15 requerido)",
            "Ahora puedes arrastrar y colocar para reorganizar tus sesiones o tus sitios.",
            "Por favor califica Tab Space en el Mac App Store si te gusta la aplicación.",
            "Los atajos de Tab Space no funcionan cuando la barra de dirección de Safarí está vacía. TabSpace interpreta una página vacía como algo especial donde la extensión no ha sido cargada."
        ],
        "loading": "Cargando...",
        "ignore-pinned-tabs": "Ignorar las páginas web ancladas al guardar las pestañas",
        "ignore-duplicated-tabs": "No guardar pestañas duplicadas (inclusive aquellas en diferentes sesiones)",
        "save-all-windows": "Guardar las pestañas de todas las ventanas",
        "shift-shortcuts": "Activar atajos with Ctrl + Shift",
        "disable-shortcuts": "Inhabilitar los atajos",
        "shortcuts": "Atajos",
        "shortcutTip": "Nota: Los atajos no funcionan cuándo la barra de direcciones de Safari está vacía.",
        "ctrlL": "Cerrar las pestañas de la izquierda",
        "ctrlR": "Cerrar las pestañas de la derecha",
        "ctrlQ": "Cerrar todas las demás pestañas",
        "ctrlC": "Abrir en Chrome",
        "ctrlW": "Abrir en Edge",
        "ctrlF": "Abrir en Firefox",
        "ctrlI": "Abrir en el navegador Brave",
        "ctrlT": "Abrir Tab Space",
        "ctrlB": "Guardar el texto seleccionado para Bear",
        "goTip": "Si solo deseas configurar Tab Space como página predeterminada cuando se abre una nueva pestaña, utiliza la dirección \"http://mytab.space/redirect.html\".",
        "saveAndCloseTabs": "Guardar y cerrar las pestañas",
        "saveAndKeepTabs": "Guardar y mantener las pestañas",
        "saveCurrentTab": "Guardar la pestaña actual",
        "recentlySaved": "Guardados Recientemente",
        "favorites": "Favorites",
        "activeTabs": "Pestañas Activas",
        "openSafariPref": "Abrir las preferencias de extensión en Safari",
        "appIntroduction": "Creado para mejorar la productividad de tu navegación web.",
        "upgradeSafari": "Tab Space requiere al menos Safari 12.1.\n Por favor actualiza Safari."
    },
    "da": {
        "saveAt": "Gemt ved",
        "restore": "Gendan",
        "delete": "Slet",
        "restoreAndDel": "Gendan & slet",
        "contact": "Kontakt",
        "settings": "Indstillinger",
        "back": "Tilbage",
        "about": "Om",
        "all": "Alle",
        "tagPrompt": "Tilføj tags her...",
        "export": "Eksport",
        "import": "Import",
        "cancel": "Annullere",
        "exportTitle": "Tab Space eksporteret faner",
        "exportHTML": "Eksporter som HTML",
        "exportJSON": "Eksporter backup fil",
        "exportText": "Kopier som tekst",
        "exportMD": "Kopier som Markdown",
        "loseTabs": "Mistet dine faner? Måske har en opgradering af Tab Space lige fundet sted, vent venligst et øjeblik og genindlæs siden ...",
        "manuallyMigrate": "Migrere manuelt sessions før Tab Space 3.5",
        "migrateTip": "Eller gå til indstillinger og migrere manuelt ældre sessions",
        "tips": "Tips:",
        "loading": "indlæser...",
        "ignore-pinned-tabs": "Ignorer fastgjorte web sider under lagring af faner",
        "save-all-windows": "Gem faner fra alle vinduer",
        "disable-shortcuts": "Deaktiver genveje",
        "shortcuts": "Genveje",
        "shortcutTip": "OBS: genveje fungerer ikke når Safari´s adressefeltet er tomt.",
        "ctrlL": "Luk faner venstre for",
        "ctrlR": "Luk faner højre for",
        "ctrlQ": "Luk alle andre faner",
        "ctrlC": "Åbn i Chrome",
        "ctrlF": "Åbn i Firefox",
        "ctrlI": "Åbn i Brave Browser",
        "ctrlT": "Åbn Tab Space",
        "ctrlB": "Gem markeret tekst til Bear",
        "goTip": "Hvis du ønsker at indstille Tab Space som startsiden af en ny fane, brug venligst adressen \"http://mytab.space/redirect.html\".",
        "saveAndCloseTabs": "Gem & luk faner",
        "saveAndKeepTabs": "Gem & behold faner",
        "saveCurrentTab": "Gem nuværende fane",
        "openSafariPref": "Åben i Safari´s udvidelses præferencer",
        "appIntroduction": "Skabt for forbedringen af din web browsings produktivitet."
    },
    "pl": {
        "saveAt": "Zapisano",
        "restore": "Przywróć",
        "delete": "Usuń",
        "restoreAndDel": "Przywróć i usuń",
        "contact": "Kontakt",
        "settings": "Ustawienia",
        "back": "Powrót",
        "about": "O nas",
        "all": "Wszystkie",
        "tagPrompt": "Dodaj tagi...",
        "whatsNew": "<strong style='color: salmon'>Nowość</strong>",
        "export": "Eksportuj",
        "import": "Importuj",
        "cancel": "Anuluj",
        "exportTitle": "Wyeksportowane karty Tab Space",
        "exportHTML": "Eksportuj jako HTML",
        "exportJSON": "Eksportuj kopię zapasową",
        "exportText": "Kopiuj jako tekst",
        "exportMD": "Kopiuj jako Markdown",
        "loseTabs": "Straciłeś swoje karty? Tab Space jest prawdopodobnie uaktualniany. Proszę poczekaj chwilę, a następnie odśwież stronę ...",
        "manuallyMigrate": "Przenieś sesje ręcznie przed Tab Space 3.5",
        "migrateTip": "Lub przejdź do ustawień i przenieś stare sesje ręcznie",
        "tips": "Podpowiedzi:",
        "tipContents": [
            "Jeśli klikniesz \"zapisz karty\" i żadna z kart nie zostanie zapisana, to dlatego, że Tab Space właśnie został zaktualizowany. Zrestartuj Safari, aby móc używać Tab Space ponownie.",
            "Twoje sesje zostały zsynchronizowane pomiędzy wszystkimi urządzeniami w iCloud. (wymagany macOS 10.15)",
            "Teraz możesz Przeciągać i Upuszczać swoje sesje i strony, aby dowolnie nimi zarządzać.",
            "Proszę oceń Tab Space w Mac App Store jeśli podoba ci się aplikacja.",
            "Skróty Tab Space nie działają gdy pasek adresu Safari jest pusty. Pusty pasek adresu oznacza specjalną stronę, która nie obsługuje rozszerzeń."
        ],
        "loading": "ładowanie...",
        "ignore-pinned-tabs": "Ignoruj przypięte strony podczas zapisywania kart",
        "ignore-duplicated-tabs": "Nie zapisuj zduplikowanych kart (nawet w różnych sesjach)",
        "save-all-windows": "Zapisz karty ze wszystkich okien",
        "shift-shortcuts": "Aktywuj skróty za pomocą Ctrl + Shift",
        "disable-shortcuts": "Wyłącz skróty",
        "shortcuts": "Skróty",
        "shortcutTip": "Notatka: skróty nie działają, gdy pasek adresu Safari jest pusty.",
        "ctrlL": "Zamknij karty z lewej strony",
        "ctrlR": "Zamknij karty z prawej strony",
        "ctrlQ": "Zamknij wszystkie inne karty",
        "ctrlC": "Otwórz w Chrome",
        "ctrlW": "Otwórz w Microsoft Edge",
        "ctrlF": "Otwórz w Firefox",
        "ctrlI": "Otwórz w Brave Browser",
        "ctrlT": "Otwórz Tab Space",
        "ctrlB": "Zapisz zaznaczony tekst w Bear",
        "goTip": "Jeśli chcesz ustawić Tab Space jako domyślną stronę nowej karty, użyj adresu \"http://mytab.space/redirect.html\".",
        "saveAndCloseTabs": "Zapisz i zamknij karty",
        "saveAndKeepTabs": "Zapisz i pozostaw karty",
        "saveCurrentTab": "Zapisz obecną kartę",
        "recentlySaved": "Ostatnio zapisane",
        "favorites": "Ulubione",
        "activeTabs": "Aktywne karty",
        "openSafariPref": "Otwórz w Ustawieniach Rozszerzeń Safari",
        "appIntroduction": "Urodzeni, aby poprawić wydajności przeglądania stron internetowych.",
        "upgradeSafari": "Tab Space wymaga co najmniej Safari 12.1.\n Proszę uaktualnij Safari."
    },
    "ru": {
        "saveAt": "Сохранено в",
        "restore": "Восстановить",
        "delete": "Удалить",
        "restoreAndDel": "Восстановить и Удалить",
        "contact": "Контакты",
        "settings": "Настройки",
        "back": "Назад",
        "about": "О Нас",
        "all": "Все",
        "tagPrompt": "Добавить теги тут",
        "whatsNew": "Что <strong style='color: salmon'>Нового</strong>",
        "export": "Экспортировать",
        "import": "Импортировать",
        "cancel": "Отменить",
        "exportTitle": "Tab Space Экспортированные вкладки",
        "exportHTML": "Экспортировать как HTML",
        "exportJSON": "Экспортировать резервную копию",
        "exportText": "Скопировать как Текст",
        "exportMD": "Скопировать как Markdown",
        "loseTabs": "Потеряли свои вкладки, Возможно Tab Space просто обновился, подождите и перезапустите … ",
        "manuallyMigrate": "Переместите в ручную сеанс ранее Tab Space 3.5",
        "migrateTip": "Или перейдите в настройки и перенесите старый сеанс в ручную",
        "tips": "Советы:",
        "tipContents": [
            "Если вы нажали \"сохранить вкладки\" и обнаружили что вкладки не сохранились, это потому-что Tab Space только что обновился, пожалуйста перезапустите Safari, что-бы заработало.",
            "Ваш сеанс синхронизирован со всеми вашими устройствами через iCloud. (Требуется macOS 10.15)",
            "Вы теперь можете перетаскивать ссылки для организации сеансов или сайтов.",
            "Пожалуйста оцените Tab Space на Mac App Store, если вам нравится это приложение.",
            "Быстрые комбинации Tab Space не будут работать при пустой поисковой строке Safari. Поскольку пустая поисковая строка означает особую страницу где расширения не работают. "
        ],
        "loading": "Загрузка…",
        "ignore-pinned-tabs": "Игнорировать закрепленные сайты, сохраняя вкладки",
        "save-all-windows": "Сохранить вкладки из всех окон.",
        "disable-shortcuts": "Отключить быстрые комбинации",
        "shortcuts": "Быстрые комбинации",
        "shortcutTip": "Приметьте: быстрые комбинации не работают, при пустой поисковой строке Safari.",
        "ctrlL": "Закрыть левую вкладку",
        "ctrlR": "Закрыть правую вкладку",
        "ctrlQ": "Закрыть все другие вкладки",
        "ctrlC": "Открыть в Chrome",
        "ctrlF": "Открыть в Firefox",
        "ctrlI": "Открыть в Brave Browser",
        "ctrlT": "Открыть Tab Space",
        "ctrlB": "Сохранить выбранный текст в Bear",
        "goTip": "Если вы хотите использовать Tab Space по умолчанию как страницу новой вкладки, пожалуйста перейдите по ссылке: \"http://mytab.space/redirect.html\".",
        "saveAndCloseTabs": "Сохранить и Закрыть Вкладки",
        "saveAndKeepTabs": "Сохранить и Оставить Вкладки",
        "saveCurrentTab": "Сохранить Текущую Вкладку",
        "openSafariPref": "Открыть в Настройках Расширений Safari",
        "appIntroduction": "Рождены для улучшения Вашей продуктивности."
    },
    "tr": {
        "saveAt": "Kayıt edilme zamanı",
        "restore": "Geri Getir",
        "delete": "Sil",
        "restoreAndDel": "Geri Getir & Sil",
        "contact": "İletişime Geç",
        "settings": "Ayarlar",
        "back": "Geri",
        "about": "Hakkımızda",
        "all": "Hepsi",
        "tagPrompt": "Buraya etiket ekle...",
        "whatsNew": "<strong style='color: salmon'>Yenilikler</strong>",
        "export": "Dışarıya aktar",
        "import": "İçeriye Aktar",
        "cancel": "İptal",
        "exportTitle": "Tab Space dışarıya aktarılmış sekmeler",
        "exportHTML": "HTML olarak dışarıya aktar",
        "exportJSON": "Yedekleme olarak aktar",
        "exportText": "Text olarak kopyala",
        "exportMD": "Markdown olarak kopyala",
        "loseTabs": "Sekmelerini mi kayıp etdin? Tab Space gücellenmiş olabilir, lütfen bekleyin ve sayfayı yenileyin...",
        "manuallyMigrate": "El ile Tab Space 3.5 oturumlarınızı geçirin",
        "migrateTip": " Veya ayarlara gidin ve el ile eski oturumlarınızı taşıyın",
        "tips": "İpuçları:",
        "tipContents": [
            "Eğer \"save tabs\" tıklayıp hiç kayıtlı sekme bulamadıysanız, bunun nedeni Tab Space yeni güncellenmiş olmasıdır, lütfen Safari'yi yeniden başlatın. ",
            "Oturumlarınız bütün cihazlarınız arasında iCloud üzerinden senkronize oluyor. (macOS 10.15 gerektirir)",
            "Artık Tut ve Sürükle yaparak oturumlarınızı ve websitelerinizi organize edebilirsiniz.",
            "Lütfen Tab Space'yi Mac App Store üzerinden yorumlamayı unutmayın.",
            "Safari adres çubuğu boş iken kısayollar çalışmaz. Bunun nedeni boş adres çubuğu Safari uzantılarını bloklar."
        ],
        "loading": "yükleniyor...",
        "ignore-pinned-tabs": "Kayıt ederken iğnelenmiş sekmeleri es geç",
        "ignore-duplicated-tabs": "Aynı adresli sekmeleri kayıt etme (farklı oturumlar için dahi geçerlidir)",
        "save-all-windows": "Bütün pencerelerden her sekmeyi kayıt et",
        "disable-shortcuts": "Kısayolları etkisiz bırak",
        "shortcuts": "Kısayollar",
        "shortcutTip": "Not: Safari adres çubuğu boş iken kısayollar çalışmaz.",
        "ctrlL": "Sol sekmeleri kapat",
        "ctrlR": "Sağ sekmeleri kapat",
        "ctrlQ": "Bütün öteki sekmeleri kapat",
        "ctrlC": "Chrome da aç",
        "ctrlF": "Firefox da aç",
        "ctrlI": "Brave Browser da aç",
        "ctrlT": "Tab Space'yi aç",
        "ctrlB": "Seçilmiş metni Bear'a kayıt et",
        "goTip": "Tab Space'i varsayılan yeni sekme olarak ayarlamak için, lütfen bu adresi kullanın \"http://mytab.space/redirect.html\".",
        "saveAndCloseTabs": "Kayıt Et & Sekmeleri Kapat",
        "saveAndKeepTabs": "Kayıt Et & Sekmeleri Açık Bırak",
        "saveCurrentTab": "Bu Sekmeyi Kayıt Et",
        "recentlySaved": "Yeni Kayıtlar",
        "favorites": "Favoriler",
        "openSafariPref": "Safari Uzatma Ayarlarında Aç",
        "appIntroduction": "Internet tarama verimliğinizi artırmak için yaratıldı.",
        "upgradeSafari": "Tab Space en azından Safari 12.1. gerektirir\n Lütfen Safari'yi güncelleyin."
    },
    "de": {
        "saveAt": "Gespeichert Unter",
        "restore": "Wiederherstellen",
        "delete": "Löschen",
        "restoreAndDel": "Wiederherstellen & Löschen",
        "contact": "Kontakt",
        "settings": "Einstellungen",
        "back": "Zurück",
        "about": "Über",
        "all": "Alles",
        "tagPrompt": "Füge hier Tags hinzu...",
        "whatsNew": "Was gibt's <strong style='color: salmon'>Neues</strong>",
        "export": "Exportieren",
        "import": "Importieren",
        "cancel": "Abbrechen",
        "exportTitle": "Tab Space exportierte Tabs",
        "exportHTML": "als HTML exportieren",
        "exportJSON": "Backup Datei exportieren",
        "exportText": "als Text kopieren",
        "exportMD": "als Markdown kopieren",
        "loseTabs": "Sind deine Tabs verschwunden? Vielleicht führt Tab Space im Moment gerade ein Upgrade durch, bitte warte einen Moment und lade es erneut...",
        "manuallyMigrate": "Manuell Sitzungen vor Tab Space 3.5 migrieren",
        "migrateTip": "Oder gehe zu Einstellungen, um dort vergangene vergangene Sitzungen zu migrieren",
        "tips": "Tips:",
        "tipContents": [
            "Wenn du \"Tabs speichern\" drückst, aber keine Tabs gespeichert wurden, liegt es daran, dass Tab Space gerade aktualisiert wurde. Bitte schließe Safari und starte es erneut, um es zu aktivieren",
            "Deine Sitzungen sind nun auf all deinen Geräten über iCloud synchronisiert. (macOS 10.15 wird benötigt)",
            "Du kannst nun Drag and Drop nutzen, um deine Sitzungen und Seiten zu reorganisieren.",
            "Bitte bewerte Tab Space im Mac App Store, wenn dir die App gefällt.",
            "Tab Space Shortcuts funktionieren nicht, wenn die Safari Address-Leiste leer ist. Denn eine leere Adress-Leiste bedeutet, dass eine besondere Seite offen ist. Hier können Erweiterungen nicht geladen werden."
        ],
        "loading": "Lädt...",
        "ignore-pinned-tabs": "Ignoriere gepinnte Webseiten, wenn Tabs gespeichert werden",
        "ignore-duplicated-tabs": "Speichere keine duplizierten Tabs (bezieht sich auch auf die in anderen Sitzungen gespeicherten)",
        "save-all-windows": "Sichere Tabs aus allen Fenstern",
        "disable-shortcuts": "Deaktiviere Shortcuts",
        "shortcuts": "Shortcuts",
        "shortcutTip": "Anmerkung: Shortcuts funktionieren nicht, wenn die Safari Adress-Leiste leer ist.",
        "ctrlL": "Schließe Tabs links",
        "ctrlR": "Schließe Tabs rechts",
        "ctrlQ": "Schließe alle anderen Tabs",
        "ctrlC": "Öffne in Chrome",
        "ctrlF": "Öffne in Firefox",
        "ctrlI": "Öffne in Brave Browser",
        "ctrlT": "Öffne Tab Space",
        "ctrlB": "Speichere ausgewählten Text in Bear",
        "goTip": "Wenn du Tab Space als Standardseite für einen neuen Tab einstellen willst, öffne folgende Adresse \"http://mytab.space/redirect.html\".",
        "saveAndCloseTabs": "Speichern & Tabs schließen",
        "saveAndKeepTabs": "Speichern & Tabs behalten",
        "saveCurrentTab": "Aktuellen Tab speichern",
        "recentlySaved": "Vor kurzem gespeicherte",
        "favorites": "Favoriten",
        "openSafariPref": "Öffne in Safari-Erweiterungen Einstellungen",
        "appIntroduction": "Geboren, um deine Webbrowsing-Produktivität zu steigern.",
        "upgradeSafari": "Tab Space benötigt mindestens Safari 12.1.\n Bitte upgrade dein Safari."
    },
    "sv": {
        "saveAt": "Sparad",
        "restore": "Återskapa",
        "delete": "Ta bort",
        "restoreAndDel": "Återskapa & ta bort",
        "contact": "Kontakt",
        "settings": "Inställningar",
        "back": "Tillbaka",
        "about": "Om",
        "all": "Alla",
        "tagPrompt": "Lägg till taggar här...",
        "whatsNew": "<strong style='color: salmon'>Nyheter</strong>",
        "export": "Exportera",
        "import": "Importera",
        "cancel": "Avbryt",
        "exportTitle": "Tab Space Exporterade flikar",
        "exportHTML": "Exportera som HTML",
        "exportJSON": "Exportera backup-fil",
        "exportText": "Kopiera som Text",
        "exportMD": "Kopiera som Markdown",
        "loseTabs": "Är dina flikar borta? Tab Space kanske precis uppgraderats, vänta en stund och ladda om på nytt ...",
        "manuallyMigrate": "Manuellt migrerade sessioner från innan Tab Space 3.5",
        "migrateTip": "Eller gå till inställningar och manuellt migrera en gammal session",
        "tips": "Tips:",
        "tipContents": [
            "Om du trycker på \"Spara flikar\" och inga flikar sparas är det för att Tab Space precis uppgraderats. Starta om Safari för att aktivera det igen.",
            "Dina sessioner är nu synkade till alla dina enheter i iCloud (kräver macOS 10.15)",
            "Du kan dra och släppa för att organisera om dina sessioner och sidor",
            "Betygsätt gärna Tab Space i Mac Appstore om du gillar detta program",
            "Tab Space kortkommandon kommer inte fungera om Safaris adressfält är tomt. Detta för att ett tomt adressfält laddar in en speciell sida som inte laddar in Safaris tillägg."
        ],
        "loading": "laddar...",
        "ignore-pinned-tabs": "Hoppa över nålade sidor när flikar sparas",
        "ignore-duplicated-tabs": "Spara inte duplicerade flikar (även om det är olika sessioner)",
        "save-all-windows": "Spara flikar från alla fönster",
        "disable-shortcuts": "Stäng av kortkommandon",
        "shortcuts": "Kortkommandon",
        "shortcutTip": "Notera: Kortkommandon fungerar inte när adressfältet i Safari är tomt..",
        "ctrlL": "Stäng flikarna till vänster",
        "ctrlR": "Stäng flikarna till höger",
        "ctrlQ": "Stäng alla andra flikar",
        "ctrlC": "Öppna i Chrome",
        "ctrlF": "Öppna i Firefox",
        "ctrlI": "Öppna i Brave Browser",
        "ctrlT": "Öppna Tab Space",
        "ctrlB": "Spara markerad text till Bear",
        "goTip": "Om du vill sätta Tab Space som din startsida när en ny flik öppnas, använd följande adress: \"http://mytab.space/redirect.html\".",
        "saveAndCloseTabs": "Spara & stäng flikar",
        "saveAndKeepTabs": "Spara & behåll flikar",
        "saveCurrentTab": "Spara nuvarande flik",
        "recentlySaved": "Nyligen sparade",
        "favorites": "Favoriter",
        "openSafariPref": "Öppna i Safaris inställningar för tillägg",
        "appIntroduction": "Skapad för att förbättra din produktivitet på webben.",
        "upgradeSafari": "Tab Space kräver minst Safari 12.1.\n Vänligen uppgradera Safari.",
        "activeTabs": "Aktiva flikar",
        "ctrlW": "Öppna i Edge",
        "shift-shortcuts": "Använd Ctrl + Shift för kortkommandon"
    },
    "it": {
        "saveAt": "Salvato il",
        "restore": "Ripristina",
        "delete": "Elimina",
        "restoreAndDel": "Ripristina ed Elimina",
        "contact": "Contatti",
        "settings": "Impostazioni",
        "back": "Indietro",
        "about": "About",
        "all": "Tutto",
        "tagPrompt": "Aggiungi i tag qui...",
        "whatsNew": "Cosa c'è di <strong style='color: salmon'>Nuovo</strong>",
        "export": "Esporta",
        "import": "Importa",
        "cancel": "Annulla",
        "exportTitle": "Tab Space Exported Tabs",
        "exportHTML": "Esporta come HTML",
        "exportJSON": "Esporta file di backup",
        "exportText": "Copia come Testo",
        "exportMD": "Copia come Markdown",
        "loseTabs": "Hai perso le tue tab? Forse Tab Space si è appena aggiornato, aspetta un momento e ricarica la pagina ...",
        "manuallyMigrate": "Migra sessioni precedenti a Tab Space 3.5",
        "migrateTip": "O vai nelle impostazioni per migrare da sessioni vecchie",
        "tips": "Suggerimenti:",
        "tipContents": [
            "Se hai selezionato \"Salva le Tab\" e non hai trovato le tab salvate, è perchè Tab Space si è appena aggiornato. Riavvia Safari per rendere effettivo l'aggiornamento. ",
            "Le tue sessioni sono ora sincronizzate su tutti i tuoi device con iCloud (richiede macOS 10.15)",
            "Puoi ora usare il Drag and Drop per riorganizzare le tue sessioni o i tuoi siti",
            "Per favore, dai un voto a Tab Space sul Mac App Store se ti piace quest'app.",
            "Le scorciatoie di Tab Space non funzionano quando la barra di navigazione di Safari è vuota. Questo perchè quando la barra di navigazione è vuota si è in una speciale pagina dove le estensioni sono disattivate"
        ],
        "loading": "caricamento...",
        "ignore-pinned-tabs": "Ignora le pagine web ancorate quando si salvano le tab",
        "ignore-duplicated-tabs": "Non salvare le tab duplicate (anche quelle di sessioni differenti)",
        "save-all-windows": "Salva le tab di tutte le finestre",
        "disable-shortcuts": "Disattiva le scorciatoie",
        "shortcuts": "Scorciatoie da tastiera",
        "shortcutTip": "Nota: le scorciatoie non funzionano quando la barra degli indirizzi è vuota.",
        "ctrlL": "Chiudi le tab a sinistra",
        "ctrlR": "Chiudi le tab a destra",
        "ctrlQ": "Chiudi tutte le altre tab",
        "ctrlC": "Apri in Chrome",
        "ctrlF": "Apri in Firefox",
        "ctrlI": "Apri in Brave Browser",
        "ctrlT": "Apri Tab Space",
        "ctrlB": "Salva il testo selezionato su Bear",
        "goTip": "Se vuoi impostare Tab Space come pagina predefinita di una nuova tab, usa questo indirizzo \"http://mytab.space/redirect.html\".",
        "saveAndCloseTabs": "Salva e chiudi le Tab",
        "saveAndKeepTabs": "Salva e tieni aperte le Tab",
        "saveCurrentTab": "Salva la Tab corrente",
        "recentlySaved": "Salvate recentemente",
        "favorites": "Preferiti",
        "openSafariPref": "Apri nelle preferenze delle estensioni di Safari",
        "appIntroduction": "Nato per migliorare la tua produttività nel browser.",
        "upgradeSafari": "Tab Space richiede la versione di Safari 12.1.\n Per favore, aggiorna Safari."
    },
    "ko": {
        "saveAt": "저장 시점",
        "restore": "복원",
        "delete": "삭제",
        "restoreAndDel": "복원 후 삭제",
        "contact": "Contact",
        "settings": "설정",
        "back": "뒤로 가기",
        "about": "About",
        "all": "전체",
        "tagPrompt": "여기에 태그 달기...",
        "whatsNew": "<strong style='color: salmon'>새소식</strong>",
        "export": "내보내기",
        "import": "불러오기",
        "cancel": "취소",
        "exportTitle": "Tab Space에서 내보낸 탭",
        "exportHTML": "HTML로 내보내기",
        "exportJSON": "백업 파일 내보내기",
        "exportText": "텍스트로 복사",
        "exportMD": "마크다운으로 복사",
        "loseTabs": "탭이 보이지 않습니까? Tab Space가 방금 업그레이드 되어 아직 안 보일 수 있습니다. 잠시 기다린 후 페이지를 새로 고쳐보세요...",
        "manuallyMigrate": "Tab Space 3.5 이전의 세션은 수동으로 이전해야 합니다",
        "migrateTip": "또는, 설정에 가서 수동으로 이전 세션을 이전하세요",
        "tips": "팁:",
        "tipContents": [
            "Tab Space가 방금 업그레이드 된 경우 \"탭 저장\"을 클릭해도 탭이 저장되지 않을 수 있습니다. Safari를 재시작하여 활성화 하십시오. ",
            "저장된 세션은 이제 iCloud를 통해 여러분이 연결한 모든 장치로 동기화 됩니다. (macOS 10.15 필요)",
            "드래그 앤 드롭으로 세션이나 사이트 위치를 바꿀 수 있습니다.",
            "Tab Space가 마음에 드신다면 Mac App Store에 평가를 남겨주세요.",
            "Safari 주소창이 비어 있으면 Tab Space 단축키가 작동하지 않습니다. 빈 주소창은 확장 기능이 작동하지 않는 특수 페이지를 뜻하기 때문입니다."
        ],
        "loading": "불러오는 중...",
        "ignore-pinned-tabs": "고정탭은 저장하지 않기",
        "ignore-duplicated-tabs": "중복탭 저장하지 않기 (다른 세션의 탭 포함)",
        "save-all-windows": "모든 창의 탭 저장",
        "disable-shortcuts": "단축키 비활성화",
        "shortcuts": "단축키",
        "shortcutTip": "주의: Safari 주소창이 비어 있으면 단축키가 작동하지 않습니다.",
        "ctrlL": "좌측 모든 탭 닫기",
        "ctrlR": "우측 모든 탭 닫기",
        "ctrlQ": "현재 탭을 제외한 모든 탭 닫기",
        "ctrlC": "Chrome에서 열기",
        "ctrlF": "Firefox에서 열기",
        "ctrlI": "Brave 브라우저에서 열기",
        "ctrlT": "Tab Space 열기",
        "ctrlB": "선택된 텍스트를 Bear에 저장",
        "goTip": "Tab Space를 새 탭의 기본 페이지로 설정하려면 \"http://mytab.space/redirect.html\" 주소를 사용하세요.",
        "saveAndCloseTabs": "모든 탭 저장하고 닫기",
        "saveAndKeepTabs": "모든 탭 저장하고 유지",
        "saveCurrentTab": "현재 탭 저장",
        "recentlySaved": "최근 저장 내역",
        "favorites": "즐겨찾기",
        "activeTabs": "열려있는 탭",
        "openSafariPref": "Safari 확장 기능 설정 열기",
        "appIntroduction": "웹 브라우징의 생산성 향상을 위해 태어났습니다.",
        "upgradeSafari": "Tab Sapce는 Safari 12.1 이상에서 동작합니다.\nSafari를 업그레이드 해주세요."
    },
    "ar-ae": {
        "saveAt": "تم الحفظ في",
        "restore": "استعد",
        "delete": "احذف",
        "restoreAndDel": "استعادة و حذف",
        "contact": "جهة الاتصال",
        "settings": "الإعدادات",
        "back": "رجوع",
        "about": "حول",
        "all": "الكل",
        "tagPrompt": "إضافة علامات هنا",
        "export": "اخراج",
        "import": "ادخال",
        "cancel": "إلغاء",
        "exportTitle": "علامات التبويب التي تم اخراجها",
        "exportHTML": " HTML اخراج بلغه",
        "exportJSON": "اخراج ملف النسخ الاحتياطي",
        "exportText": "نسخ كنص",
        "exportMD": "Markdown نسخ",
        "loseTabs": "هل فقدت علامات التبويب الخاصة بك؟ ربما تمت ترقية Tab Space للتو ، يرجى الانتظار قليلاً  والتحديث",
        "ctrlL": "إغلاق علامات التبويب اليسرى",
        "ctrlR": "إغلاق علامات التبويب اليمنى",
        "ctrlQ": "إغلاق كافة علامات التبويب الأخرى",
        "ctrlC": " chrome افتح في",
        "ctrlW": "Edge افتح في",
        "ctrlF": "Firefox افتح في",
        "ctrlI": "Brave افتح في",
        "ctrlT": "Tab Space افتح"
    },
    "nl": {
        "saveAt": "Bewaard op",
        "restore": "Herstel",
        "delete": "Verwijder",
        "restoreAndDel": "Herstel & Verwijder",
        "contact": "Contact",
        "settings": "Instellingen",
        "back": "Terug",
        "about": "Over",
        "all": "Alle",
        "tagPrompt": "Voeg hier tags toe...",
        "whatsNew": "Wat is <strong style='color: salmon'>Nieuw</strong>",
        "export": "Exporteer",
        "import": "Importeer",
        "cancel": "Annuleer",
        "exportTitle": "Tab Space Geëxporteerde Tabbladen",
        "exportHTML": "Exporteer als HTML",
        "exportJSON": "Exporteer back-up bestand",
        "exportText": "Kopieer als Tekst",
        "exportMD": "Kopieer als markering",
        "loseTabs": "Ben je je tabbladen kwijt? Misschien is Tab Space net geüpgraded, wacht even en ververs...",
        "manuallyMigrate": "Handmatige migratie van sessies vóór Tab Space 3.5",
        "migrateTip": "Of ga naar de instellingen en migreer handmatig oude sessies",
        "tips": "Tips:",
        "tipContents": [
            "Als je op ‘Bewaar tabbladen' drukt en je ziet dat er geen tabbladen zijn opgeslagen, is het omdat Tab Space net is geüpgraded, start dan alsjeblieft Safari opnieuw op om het in te schakelen. ",
            "Uw sessies worden nu op al uw apparaten gesynchroniseerd met iCloud. (macOS 10.15 vereist)",
            "U kunt nu gebruik maken van Drag and Drop om uw sessies of sites te reorganiseren.",
            "Beoordeel Tab Space op de Mac App Store als je dit programma leuk vindt.",
            "Tab Space shortcuts werkt niet als de adresbalk van Safari leeg is. Omdat een lege adresbalk een speciale pagina betekent waardoor de extensie niet kon worden geladen."
        ],
        "loading": "laden....",
        "ignore-pinned-tabs": "Negeer vastgepinde webpagina's tijdens het opslaan van tabbladen",
        "ignore-duplicated-tabs": "Sla geen dubbele tabbladen op (zelfs niet voor de verschillende sessies)",
        "save-all-windows": "Bewaar tabbladen van alle vensters",
        "shift-shortcuts": "Trigger snelkoppelingen met Ctrl + Shift",
        "disable-shortcuts": "Schakel snelkoppelingen uit",
        "shortcuts": "Snelkoppelingen",
        "shortcutTip": "Opmerking: snelkoppelingen werken niet als de adresbalk van Safari leeg is.",
        "ctrlL": "Sluit de linkertabbladen",
        "ctrlR": "Sluit de rechtertabbladen",
        "ctrlQ": "Sluit alle andere tabbladen",
        "ctrlB": "Geselecteerde tekst opslaan in Bear",
        "goTip": "Als u gewoon Tab Space wilt instellen als de standaardpagina van een nieuw tabblad, gebruik dan het adres \"http://mytab.space/redirect.html\".",
        "saveAndCloseTabs": "Bewaar & sluit tabbladen",
        "saveAndKeepTabs": "Bewaar & behoud tabbladen",
        "saveCurrentTab": "Bewaar huidig tabblad",
        "recentlySaved": "Onlangs bewaard",
        "favorites": "Favorieten",
        "activeTabs": "Actieve Tabbladen",
        "appIntroduction": "Gemaakt om de productiviteit van het surfen op het web te verbeteren.",
        "upgradeSafari": "Tab Space vereist ten minste Safari 12.1.\n Gelieve Safari te upgraden."
    },
    "fr": {
        "saveAt": "Sauvegarder dans",
        "location": "Adresse: ",
        "newSession": "Nouvelle Session",
        "restore": "Restaurer",
        "delete": "Supprimer",
        "restoreAndDel": "Restaurer & Supprimer",
        "contact": "Contact",
        "settings": "Paramètres",
        "back": "Retour",
        "about": "À propos",
        "all": "Tout",
        "movePrompt": "Déplacer la session",
        "tagPrompt": "Ajouter des tags ici...",
        "editPrompt": "Modifier la session",
        "topPrompt": "Déplacer en haut",
        "mergePrompt": "Fusionner avec la session...",
        "whatsNew": "Ce qui est <strong style='color: salmon'>Nouveau</strong>",
        "export": "Exporter",
        "import": "Importer",
        "cancel": "Annuler",
        "exportTitle": "Exporter en Tab Space",
        "exportHTML": "Exporter en HTML",
        "exportJSON": "Exporter dans un fichier de sauvegarde",
        "exportText": "Copier en texte",
        "exportMD": "Copier en Markdown",
        "loseTabs": "Vous-avez perdu vos onglets ? Peut-être que Tab Space a été mis à jour, attendez un peu s'il vous plaît et rafraichissez votre navigateur...",
        "manuallyMigrate": "Migrez manuellement vos sessions avant Tab Space 3.5",
        "migrateTip": "Ou allez dans paramètres et migrez manuellement vos anciennes sessions",
        "tips": "Astuces:",
        "tipContents": [
            "Si vous cliquez \"Sauvergarder onglets\" et qu'aucun onglet n'est sauvegardé, c'est parce que Tab Space vient d'être mis à jour, redémarrez Safari pour le réactiver s'il vous plaît. ",
            "Vos sessions sont maintenant synchronisées sur tous vos appareils iCloud. (macOS 10.15 obligatoire)",
            "Vous pouvez maintenant utiliser Glisser-Déposer pour réorganiser vos sessions ou sites.",
            "Donnez une note à Tab Space sur le Mac App Store si vous aimez l'application.",
            "Les raccourcis Tab Space ne marcherons pas quand la barre d'adresse Safari est vide. Parce que une barre d'adresse vide est une page spéciale où les extensions ne peuvent pas êtres chargés."
        ],
        "loading": "chargement...",
        "ignore-pinned-tabs": "Ignorer les pages web épinglés en sauvegardant les onglets",
        "ignore-duplicated-tabs": "Ne pas sauvegarder les onglets dupliqués (même pour ceux présents dans des sessions différentes)",
        "save-all-windows": "Sauvegarder les onglets de toutes les fenêtres",
        "shift-shortcuts": "Activez les raccourcis avec Ctrl + Shift",
        "disable-shortcuts": "Désactiver les raccourcis",
        "shortcuts": "Raccourcis",
        "shortcutTip": "Note: Les raccourcis ne fonctionnent pas quand la barre d'adresse Safari est vide.",
        "ctrlL": "Fermer les onglets de gauche",
        "ctrlR": "Fermer les onglets de droite",
        "ctrlQ": "Fermer tous les autres onglets",
        "ctrlC": "Ouvrir dans Chrome",
        "ctrlW": "Ouvrir dans Edge",
        "ctrlF": "Ouvrir dans Firefox",
        "ctrlI": "Ouvrir dans Brave Navigateur",
        "ctrlT": "Ouvrir Tab Space",
        "ctrlB": "Sauvegarder le texte dans Bear",
        "goTip": "Si vous voulez seulement définir Tab Space comme votre page par défaut lors de l'ouverture d'un nouvel onglet, utilisez l'adresse suivante \"http://mytab.space/redirect.html\".",
        "saveAndCloseTabs": "Sauvegarder & Fermer les onglets",
        "saveAndKeepTabs": "Sauvegarder & Garder les onglets",
        "saveCurrentTab": "Sauvegarder les onglets ouverts",
        "recentlySaved": "Sauvegardés récemment",
        "favorites": "Favoris",
        "activeTabs": "Onglets ouverts",
        "openSafariPref": "Ouvrir dans les préférences d'extension Safari",
        "appIntroduction": "Née pour améliorer votre productivité sur navigateur.",
        "upgradeSafari": "Tab Space nécéssite au moins Safari 12.1.\n Mettez à jour Safari."
    },
    "ja": {
        "saveAt": "保存日時: ",
        "location": "場所: ",
        "newSession": "新しいセッション",
        "restore": "復元",
        "delete": "削除",
        "restoreAndDel": "復元と削除",
        "contact": "問い合わせ",
        "settings": "設定",
        "back": "戻る",
        "about": "詳細",
        "all": "すべて",
        "movePrompt": "セッションの移動",
        "tagPrompt": "ここにタグを入力",
        "editPrompt": "セッションの編集",
        "topPrompt": "最上部に移動",
        "mergePrompt": "ここに統合したいセッションを入力",
        "whatsNew": "<strong style='color: salmon'>新機能</strong>",
        "export": "エクスポート",
        "import": "インポート",
        "cancel": "取り消し",
        "exportTitle": "Tab Space Exported Tabs",
        "exportHTML": "HTML 形式でエクスポート",
        "exportJSON": "バックアップファイルとしてエクスポート",
        "exportText": "テキスト形式でコピー",
        "exportMD": "Markdown 形式でコピー",
        "loseTabs": "タブが表示されませんか?  先ほど Tab Space が更新されたため、データ処理に少し時間がかかっています。完了までしばらくお待ちください。",
        "manuallyMigrate": "Tab Space 3.5 以前のセッションは、手動で移行する必要があります。",
        "migrateTip": "「設定」を選択して、古いセッションを手動で移行してください。",
        "tips": "豆知識:",
        "tipContents": [
            "Tab Space が更新された直後には、「タブを保存」を選択しても保存されたタブが表示されないことがあります。その時には、Safari を再起動してください。",
            "保存されたセッションは、iCloud を有効にした機器間で同期されます（macOS 10.15 以降）",
            "セッションやサイトは、ドラッグアンドドロップで編集できます。",
            "Tab Space を気に入ったら、Mac App Store で評価をお願いします。",
            "Tab Space ショートカットは、Safari のアドレスバーが空だと動作しません。アドレスバーが空の状態で表示されているページでは、機能拡張が使えないからです。"
        ],
        "loading": "読み込み中...",
        "ignore-pinned-tabs": "タブを保存する時にピン留めされたページを無視する",
        "ignore-duplicated-tabs": "重複したタブ（別のセッションにあるものを含む）を保存しない",
        "save-all-windows": "すべてのウィンドウのタブを保存する",
        "shift-shortcuts": "Ctrl + Shift を押した時にショートカットキーを有効にする",
        "disable-shortcuts": "ショートカットキーを無効にする",
        "disable-context-menus": "コンテキストメニューを無効にする",
        "remove-site-after-click": "クリックした時に、保存されたタブをセッションから削除する",
        "shortcuts": "ショートカットキー",
        "shortcutTip": "注意: ショートカットキーは、Safari のアドレスバーが空の時には動作しません。",
        "ctrlL": "左のタブを閉じる",
        "ctrlR": "右のタブを閉じる",
        "ctrlQ": "選択しているタブ以外をすべて閉じる",
        "ctrlC": "Chrome で開く",
        "ctrlW": "Edge で開く",
        "ctrlF": "Firefox で開く",
        "ctrlI": "Brave Browser で開く",
        "ctrlT": "Tab Space を開く",
        "ctrlB": "Bear に選択中のテキストを保存する",
        "goTip": "新しいタブを開いた時に自動的に Tab Space のページを表示するには、\"http://mytab.space/redirect.html\" をデフォルトページに設定してください。",
        "saveAndCloseTabs": "タブをすべて保存して閉じる",
        "saveAndKeepTabs": "タブをすべて保存して、開いたままにする",
        "saveCurrentTab": "選択中のタブを保存する",
        "recentlySaved": "最近保存したタブ",
        "favorites": "お気に入り",
        "activeTabs": "選択中のタブ",
        "openSafariPref": "Safari 機能拡張の設定を開く",
        "appIntroduction": "ウェブ閲覧効率化のために",
        "upgradeSafari": "Tab Space は Safari 12.1 以降が必要です。\n Safari を更新してください。"
    }
}
